goliath.com 2004-04-02

# Privacy Policy

| 

This statement discloses the privacy practices for IIS.com

**Personal Information**  
IIS.COM recognizes your right to confidentiality and is committed to protecting your privacy. We will not give, rent, loan, or sell any identifiable personal information to any other third party, unless legally required to do so.

We may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services. In addition, we may use that information to contact you.

**Non-Personal Information**  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our Web site.

**Security**  
IIS uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.

**IP Addresses**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the IIS.COM domain, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**Cookies**  
We use a feature on your Internet browser called a "Cookie." Cookies are small files created on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer. We also use cookies to retrieve certain information previously provided by you to IIS.COM, so that you will not need to re-enter this information every time you visit the site. We will not use cookies to store personal/business information.

Unless you specifically tell us, we will never know who you are, even though we may assign the browser on your computer a cookie. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. IIS.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact webmaster@iis.com.
